# CAMILLE CELONE

UX/UI Designer & Front-End Developer

## **ABOUT ME**

I stumbled into the field of user experience design in college and realized I wanted to be creating things that would help people. I have since learned that I not only love creating designs to help people, but writing code as well. Whether it be sketching and prototyping or writing HTML, CSS, and Javascript, I find joy in knowing that my efforts will benefit somebody. I believe that things should be created for a purpose, and when I get to be a part of realizing that purpose, I know that the final product will be meaningful not only to the clients, but to the users as well.

## **SKILLS**

Adobe Photoshop Adobe Illustrator Adobe InDesign Adobe XD Axure **HTML CSS** Javascript Vue.js 

# **CONTACT ME**











## **EDUCATION**

**DEPAUL UNIVERSITY** 

**BS in Interactive and Social Media**, June 2018 Development Concentration GPA 3.82/4.0

MS in Human-Computer Interaction, expected in 2020

#### **EXPERIENCE**

Center for Robust Decisionmaking on Climate and Energy Policy: Research Assitant, Jan. 2017 - Present

- Develop user-configurable enhancements for a global, dynamic, geospatial data visualization platform.
- Strategize and streamline user interactions across a wide variety of data visualizations including maps and charts.
- Design highly functional, iterative, interactive prototypes using Axure.
- Create user testing protocols to test prototype iterations and identify design problems.

#### Perry Mansion Cultural Center: Wordpress Developer, Sept. 2017 – Nov. 2017

- Collaborate with client and team members to determine the needs of a new website for Perry Mansion Cultural Center.
- Co-develop a functional Wordpress site that meets the clients needs and offers a visually pleasing and engaging user interface and easy-to-use back-end for client use.

#### Arrived: UX/UI Designer, Feb. 2017 – May 2017

- Create prototypes of redesigned Arrived Android and iOS applications using Axure and Adobe Experience Design.
- Design a chatbot that integrates with Arrived applications for submission to the NYC BigApps competition.

#### Long River Gallery & Gifts: Front-End Developer

- Front-end design and development for a privately-owned fine art and craft gallery in White River Junction, Vermont
- Collaborate with back-end developer to create cohesive, client-editable platform